<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Habba 18</string>
    <string name="car_image">car_image</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">LOVE MUSIC</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 albums</string>

    <string name="horizontal_timeline">Horizontal Timeline</string>
    <string name="vertical_timeline">Vertical Timeline</string>
    <string name="horizontal_timeline_w_padding">Horizontal Timeline With Line Padding</string>
    <string name="vertical_timeline_w_padding">Vertical Timeline With Line Padding</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="quickstart_message">Click the SUBSCRIBE TO NEWS button below to subscribe to the
        news topic. Messages sent to the news topic will be received. The LOG TOKEN button logs the
        InstanceID token to logcat.</string>
    <string name="subscribe_to_news">Subscribe To News</string>
    <string name="log_token">Log Token</string>

    <string name="msg_subscribed">Subscribed to news topic</string>
    <string name="msg_token_fmt" translatable="false">InstanceID Token: %s</string>

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <!--
        This is the name that users will see when interacting with this channel.
        It should describe the category of notifications that will be sent through this channel
     -->
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name" translatable="true">News</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="last"><![CDATA[-->>]]></string>
    <string name="jump3"><![CDATA[>]]></string>
    <string name="middle">O</string>
    <string name="back3"><![CDATA[<]]></string>
    <string name="first"><![CDATA[<<--]]></string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps2">Map</string>
    <string name="About_Acharya">\n" Nurturing Aspirations Supporting Growth "\n

\nThe Sanskrit word "Acharya", which means "TEACHER", epitomizes the quintessential values of our institution, where traditional respect for teachers is of paramount importance. At our 28th year, we at Acharya Institutes, Bangalore are proud to be the choice of students from around the world.\n\n

\nGrowing Stature of Acharya\n\n

\n 120 acres of WiFi Campus
\n 13 Educational Institutions
\n 15 research centers
\n Nearly 100 programs in over 50 Academic Streams
\n Over 12,000 students for 70 countries
\n 1000+ teaching, technical and administration staff
\n Affiliated to VTU, BU, RGUHS and KSLU
\n Approved by AICTE, Council of Architecture, KSNC, INC, NCTE, PCI and Bar Council of India
\n NBA, NAAC accredited
\n Technical and Academic association with leading industry and corporate
\n Collaboration with many academic and research organizations

We are –\n
A student centric campus that attracts over 4000 aspiring youth each year from across the globe.\n
We have –\n
An atmosphere of academic excellence that draws best teaching faculty into it\n
We instill –\n
Time tested values in grooming youth into responsible human beings\n
We create –\n
An encouraging and competitive environment that enables academic growth \n\n

Our Motto\n\n

"Nurturing Aspirations Supporting Growth"\n\n

Our Vision\n\n

"Acharya Institutes, Committed to the cause of value-based education in all disciplines, envisions itself as a fountainhead of innovative human enterprise, with inspirational initiatives for Academic Excellence"</string>
    <string name="About_Habba">Arguably called the mother of all fests, Acharya Habba is the
annual techno-cultural fest organized by Acharya Institutes,
Bangalore. Spanning over a duration of a month, it draws about
25,000+ students from more than 300 colleges across
Karnataka. Home to a multi-ethnicity crowd, the campus offers
a host of opportunities for various groups from various
interests to come together and be a part of the biggest fest in
Bangalore. A strong minded group of individuals join hands to
organize the 60+ events that span across a period of one
month. Be it Music, Dance, Dramatics or Fashion, we got it all!
More than a decade old, Habba commands respect and is a
major crowd puller for all colleges in Karnataka. With its wide
variety of events and shows, it has something for everyone’s
taste and talent. Also on its attractive “resume”, is the honor of
being a launch pad to many celebrities and artistes and
continues to be a fan favorite for people to see their celebrities
perform and interact live. Not only that, we are also home to
one of the hottest and most happening music nights. The
exciting line ups of one of the best EDM artists in their fields
brings in thousands of people to watch and dance to the
exhilarating atmosphere Habba provides. Habba promises to be
an engaging experience for people of all ages and passions.
There’s something for everyone who is a part of Habba, not
matter what the magnitude of contribution is. That’s the

beauty of Acharya Habba. The most awaited fest of Bangalore is
here and it never disappoints!</string>
    <string name="left_arrow"><![CDATA[<<]]></string>
    <string name="right_arrow"><![CDATA[>>]]></string>
</resources>
